I know this news is sudden
Your feelings must be more complicated than mine
But no matter what
He's still your own flesh and blood
I haven't taken care of him for over 20 years
What right do I have now?
At least you can give him a choice
But once I take this step
there's really no coming back
They've always wanted me to go back
to take charge
to become the Boss
Right now I just want to live out
the rest of my life in peace
I don't want to go back to that world
Right now I just want to stay by your side
and never go anywhere
You won't
You won't walk down that old path again
Now you have me
and the flower shop
I'll wait for you to come home
Brother Qiang
I hear your company's been under heavy investigation lately.
So? Can you handle it?
Thanks for the concern.
They're auditing my books,
shutting down my shops,
and now a murder charge.
You do the math.
Can Chen Jiadong find any evidence against you?
Of course not.
All they'll find is garbage.
I'm a law-abiding citizen.
No evidence means no evidence.
He's got nothing.
But I do.
That bitch Zheng Baojiao
gave it to you after all.
Ah Hong.
Don't keep going down the wrong path.
Turn yourself in.
Keep this up and there's no turning back.
Hand over Zihao,
and leave everything to...
Leave it to who?
To you?
I'm not fighting you over it.
The two of us
were doing just fine before you got out.
The moment you got out, everything fell apart.
You want to be Dragon Head?
Fine.
In your next life.
I never wanted to fight you for Dragon Head.
Just hand over Zihao.
Where Zihao is is none of your damn business.
I'm thinking of taking your advice.
Taking Zihao on a trip to Europe.
Zihao's got nothing to do with this.
If you take him away,
his whole life...
How I treat my son
is none of your business, Liang Zhiqiang!
He's not your son.
He's my son.
He's your son?
Twenty years.
I raised him for twenty years.
Where the hell were you?
As long as he bears the Xie name,
he'll bear it his whole life.
He's my son.
You're just a stud.
You ask where I was for twenty years?
Don't you know?
Who were those twenty years for?
Isn't it obvious?
I did twenty years in prison for you.
Not because I'm some great guy.
I want to tell you,
I did it for my own brother.
Ah Hong, you're my brother.
Do you get that?
Don't call me Ah Hong.
Ah Hong is dead.
He died twenty years ago.
You killed him, Liang Zhiqiang.
I'm now the Dragon Head of Heyisheng.
Xie Guanhong.
My good brother Ah Hong is dead.
Then let me offer incense for him.
I'll leave in a bit
Sir, have you seen this person?
No.
Excuse me.
Have you seen this person?
Have you seen him?
Thank you.
Have you seen this person?
No, I haven't.
Take a closer look.
I want to go home
Fine
Go call your damn father
and get me out of here too
Can't you speak a little more politely?
Who the hell are you?
I'm not your mother
I'm under no obligation to coddle you
You'd better behave yourself
Just because I smile at you every day
you really think you're a big shot.
Now that's your dad's good boy.
Have you even seen what's going on out there?
If you just walk out like that,
and you'll be dead in a heartbeat.
Just stay put,
and wait for your dad.
Once he deals with those idiots,
then you can go back out there,
and be the Gang's young master again.
But I don't want to do it anymore.
I've made up my mind.
I can't be the Boss,
and I don't want to be a gangster either.
I just want to live a normal life.
A normal life?
Are you out of your mind?
Your last name is Xie.
And you want a normal life?
Are you an idiot?
What does my last name have to do with it?
I can't choose my last name,
but surely I can choose what I do.
You know,
I thought about leaving too.
But then I figured it out.
Xie Guanhong chose everything for you long ago.
Who's around you,
what clothes you wear,
who you should trust,
which path you should take.
I have no choice.
And neither do you.
Is there anything I can help you with?
Hello
Stop wandering around, will you?
Searching like this is useless.
I know about what happened to Zihao.
A Qiang, trust me, okay?
Excuse me.
Have you seen this boy?
About seventeen or eighteen.
Pretty good-looking, actually.
Have you seen him?
No, I haven't.
Thank you.
I've already requested a traffic search,
and pulled nearby security footage.
We'll find him soon.
Don't worry.
He's old enough, he'll be fine.
Hi, have you seen this boy?
No, I haven't.
Thank you.
A Qiang, just trust me, okay?
I trust you.
I'm a cop.
And I'm your brother too.
Can't you trust me?
I won't let anything happen to him.
Heyisheng is causing chaos out there right now.
If you go out, they'll definitely come after you.
You stay right here.
Are you going back?
I don't want to be Boss anymore.
I know wandering around now
is only causing you trouble.
Zihao is my son.
I can't just not look for him.
I can't wait.
Just trust me, okay?
Liang Zhiqiang
Why are you still looking for my son?